# **Andreas Marsh**

### Computer Science Honors Undergraduate Student

#### **SUMMARY**

I am a fourth-year honors student at the University of Georgia studying Computer Science and have training and experience in Java, Swift, C++, and Python programming as well as User Experience Design using Figma and Adobe XD.

I love creating applications that others can interact with and explore and have recently begun the development of a personal website/blog as a side project. Another project I have recently completed was the creation of a Cinema E-Booking system using Java, MySQL, Spring, HTML, and Bootstrap. To complete this, I worked side-by-side with a team of developers to go from creating prototypes of the system to writing the front and backend code. Feel free to check out my GitHub to see these and some of the other projects that I've been working on.

Through years of working at summer camps, I have developed great leadership, communication, and teamwork skills, being able to create environments where everybody feels both included and valued.

#### **EXPERIENCE**



### **The UGA Career Center,** Athens, GA — Freelance iOS Developer

May 2021

- added mobile event functionality to an in-development Arch Ready iOS app designed to track students' attendance of events towards completion of the Arch Ready Professionalism Certificate
- worked with Swift UIKit and Google Firebase to create an event-specific PIN system to be used to confirm asynchronous attendance



## **Glisson Camp & Retreat Center,** Dahlonega, GA — *Camp Counselor*

May 2021 - July 2021 & May 2019 - July 2019

- worked with children and adults with mild to moderate developmental disabilities
- aided in the training and coaching of other counselors
- created an environment that uplifted campers and allowed their uniqueness to shine

### **EDUCATION / CERTIFICATION**



### **The University of Georgia,** Athens, GA — BS Computer Science

August 2018 - May 2022



New Media Institute, Athens, GA — New Media Certificate (Dev Track)

### **CONTACT**

124 North Poplar St Athens, GA, 30601 (404) 502-0710 marsh.andreas.s@gmail.com

### **GITHUB / WEBSITE**

github.com/andreasmarsh

andreasmarsh.com

### **SKILLS**

**Java** 

**Swift** 

C++

Python

**Spring Framework** 

**Android Studio** 

**XCode** 

Figma/Adobe XD

**Bootstrap** 

### **HONORS & AWARDS**

**Honors Program** Member of UGA's Honor Program

August 2018 - Present

Dean's List

Spring Semester 2020

Charter Scholarship Recipient Awarded for outstanding achievement in academics to 2% of new students

#### **LANGUAGES**

**English** (high proficiency)

**German** (moderate proficiency)

August 2018 - May 2022